indexmarks.com 2013-06-05

# Privacy Policy | IndexMarks

**Privacy Policy**  
We at Indexmarks.com recognize that the privacy of your personal information is important. To that end, we have here outlined what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit Indexmarks.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

**Log Files**  
As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files includes your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Comcast), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer, Chrome or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**  
We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features.

We also use third party advertisements on Indexmarks.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geo-targeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

**DoubleClick Dart Cookies**  
We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security number, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of these ads serving on all sites by visiting: http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx

You can choose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Kaspersky Internet Security or Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs.

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

**Conditions of Use, Notices, And Revisions**  
If you choose to visit Indexmarks.com, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Policy and our Terms of Use including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of New York. Our business changes constantly. This Notice and the Terms of Use will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes.

**Information You Give Us**  
You provide us with information when you buy or communicate with customer service. For example, you provide information when you make an order; provide information in your account (and you might have more than one if you have used more than one e-mail address when shopping with us), communicate with us by phone, e-mail, or otherwise. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, phone number, and credit card information.

**eMail Communications**  
To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we often receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from Indexmarks.com, if your computer supports such capabilities. If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please contact us.

**Information From Other Sources**  
For reasons such as improving personalization of our service, we might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information.

**Automatic Information**  
Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; purchase history; the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time.
